

GRAPHIC DESIGN BY HILLARY DUYSEN

559.361.9059

hillaryduysendesigns.com

hillaryduysendesigns@hotmail.com

SUMMARY

A driven, resilient, and confident designer that is able to perform under pressure. Strong organizational, management, and communication skills. Strong technical skills in Adobe Creative Suite programs and experience in tending to deadlines with printers and vendors. Experience in a fast paced, deadline driven environment with an emphasis on details and design creativity.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Stampington & Co., Laguna Hills, Ca

Jr. Graphic Designer 2012-Present

Designing publications for an independent magazine publisher. Responsibilities include designing at least one publication a month, communicating with printing companies and distributors, creating original design concepts for new publications and marketing material, participating in photography direction, and file management.

Porterville Unified School District , Porterville, Ca

Graphic Designer 2008-2012

Designing print media for various events across the district. Main responsibilities included designing across various medias, infographics and signage.

Hillary Duysen Designs, California

Freelance Graphic Designer 2007-Present

Developing identities, print media and web files for various companies.

INTERNSHIPS

The Valley Voice

Visalia, Ca

Jr. Graphic Designer, 2011

Assisted on the layout of weekly publications, monthly magazine publications and advertisements. Responsibilities included file management, processing photos, pre-press management and general layout and design. Gained experience in deadlines, task management, and print design.

Porterville Recorder

Porterville, Ca

Jr. Graphic Designer, 2008

A three month position assisting with design and organization. Responsibilities included designing documents, advertisements and identities for companies working with the publication. I also gained experience in desiigning for various medias such as t-shirts and large format print media. An emphasis on client interaction and preparing files for offset printing.

EDUCATION

The Academy of Art University

San Francisco, Ca

Bachelor of Fine Arts in Graphic Design, 2012

An education focused on designing based on visually strong concepts. Courses include advanced typography, branding and identity, print media, packaging, web design and working with hierarchy across books and publications.